Ok, 100 ohms, the probe in parallel with it.
That means, here there are one and a half turns instead of the inductor, the output from the generator.
Ok, the first maximum at the high end is 9.3 MHz for us.
But here's what's interesting, if you touch it with your hand, the amplitude decreases.
Not interesting.
Let's go down further.
The second maximum at 6.2 to 6.3 MHz also.
I touch it, the amplitude also drops.
Going down further.
We've arrived.
A good jump.
At 1.73.
Somewhere around there.
Here's the frequency.
1.172 MHz.
And here's what's interesting, at this frequency, if you touch it, the amplitude, you can see, increases a bit.
But it doesn't drop and stays stable.
You can look closer at what'll be there.
There's something going on.
Some kind of beats.
A little more.
Somewhere around this area is where it is.